const questions = {
  questions:[
  {
    id: 1,
    question: 'waa',
    font: 'kulitan',
    options: ['Mo', 'Ní-Nî', 'Wá-wâ', 'Da'],
    correctAnswer: 'Wá-wâ',
  },
  {
    id: 1,
    question: 'waa',
    font: 'kulitan',
    options: ['Mo', 'Ní-Nî', 'Wá-wâ', 'Da'],
    correctAnswer: 'Wá-wâ',
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: 'we',
    options: ['Be', 'We', 'Wo', 'Gu' ],
    correctAnswer: 'We',
  },
{
id: 3,
question: 'wi',
options: ['Pi', 'Nu', 'Wi', 'Su' ],
correctAnswer: 'Wi',
},
{
id: 4,
question: 'wo',
options: ['Wo', 'Lang', 'Yo', 'Go' ],
correctAnswer: 'Wo',
},
{
id: 5,
question: 'wu',
options: ['Wang', 'Wu', 'Pang', 'Yu' ],
correctAnswer: 'Wu',
},
{
id: 6,
question: 'wuu',
options: ['Pá-pâ', 'Be', 'Ki', 'Wú-wû' ],
correctAnswer: 'Wú-wû',
},
{
id: 7,
question: 'Ya',
options: ['Kan', 'Ya', 'Yi', 'Yu' ],
correctAnswer: 'Ya',
},
{
  id: 8,
  question: 'yang',
  options: ['Kin', 'Yang', 'Sang', 'Sa' ],
  correctAnswer: 'Yang',
},
{
  id: 9,
  question: 'yaa',
  options: ['Gi', 'Pí-pî', 'Yá-Yâ', 'Kin' ],
  correctAnswer: 'Yá-Yâ',
},
{
  id: 10,
  question: 'ye',
  options: ['Yang', 'Kang', 'Ye', 'Po' ],
  correctAnswer: 'Ye',
},
{
  id: 11,
  question: 'yi',
  options: ['Pu', 'Má-Mâ', 'Yi', 'Ga' ],
  correctAnswer: 'Yi',
},
{
  id: 12,
  question: 'yii',
  options: ['Mang', 'Sang', 'Yí-yî', 'Pú-pû' ],
  correctAnswer: 'Yí-yî',
},
{
  id: 13,
  question: 'yo',
  options: ['Ku', 'Ngi', 'Ken', 'Yo' ],
  correctAnswer: 'Yo',
},
{
  id: 14,
  question: 'yu',
  options: ['Yu', 'Sá-Sâ', 'Ki', 'Si' ],
  correctAnswer: 'Yu',
},
{
  id: 15,
  question: 'yuu',
  options: ['Du', 'Yú-yû', 'Gu', 'Mí-Mî' ],
  correctAnswer: 'Yú-yû',
},
{
  id: 16,
  question: 'kan',
  options: ['Kan', 'Go', 'Si', 'Mo' ],
  correctAnswer: 'Kan',
},
{
  id: 17,
  question: 'kaan',
  options: ['Mu', 'Kán', 'Kan', 'Yi' ],
  correctAnswer: 'Kán',
},
{
  id: 18,
  question: 'ken',
  options: ['Nu', 'Ken', 'Bang', 'Kon' ],
  correctAnswer: 'Ken',
},
{
  id: 19,
  question: 'Kin',
  options: ['Ki', 'Mú-Mû', 'Kin', 'Su' ],
  correctAnswer: 'Kin',
},
{
  id: 20,
  question: 'kiin',
  options: ['Kín', 'Sú-Sû', 'Nang', 'Si' ],
  correctAnswer: 'Kín',
},
{
  id: 21,
  question: 'kon',
  options: ['Ku', 'Kon', 'Nu', 'Mang' ],
  correctAnswer: 'Kon',
},
{
  id: 22,
  question: 'kun',
  options: ['Tá-Tâ', 'Kun', 'Kún', 'Lu' ],
  correctAnswer: 'Kun',
},
{
  id: 23,
  question: 'kuun',
  options: ['Kun', 'Kon', 'Ke', 'Kún' ],
  correctAnswer: 'Kún',
},
{
  id: 24,
  question: 'kuun',
  options: ['Kun', 'Kon', 'Ke', 'Kún' ],
  correctAnswer: 'Kún',
},
{
  id: 25,
  question: 'kuun',
  options: ['Kun', 'Kon', 'Ke', 'Kún' ],
  correctAnswer: 'Kún',
},





]
};
  
  export default questions;